Marlon Riggs Papers, 1957-1994 M1759
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 1: Project Files
  - Subseries 8: Black Is...Black Ain't
    - BIBA Personal Interview transcripts (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Mississippi Interviews
    - BIBA Personal Interview transcripts (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - BIBA Personal Interview transcripts (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Southern California Interviews
    - BIBA Personal Interview transcripts (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - BIBA Personal Interview transcripts (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Northern California Interviews
    - Research material about Wayne Corbitt (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Research material about Angela Davis (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Research material about Anthony Davis (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Research materiall about Coco Fusco (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Research material about Henry L Gates (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Research material about H.L. Gates jnr (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Research material about Malcolm X (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Research material about Bell Hooks (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Research material about Spike Lee (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Research material about Stuart Hall (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Research material about Zora Neale Hurston (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Research material about Sdiane Bogus (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Research material about Bill T Jones (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Research material about Jaquie Jones (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Research material about P.M. Jones (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Research material about Dr. Maulina (Ron) Karenga (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Research material about Magic Johnson (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Research material about Keith Antar Mason (Plyrt) (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Research material about Paul Gilroy (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Research material about Ingrid Pollard (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Research material about Barbara Smith (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Research material about Audre Lourde (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Research material about Mike Tyson (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Research material about Thomas/Hill Hearings (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Research material about Michele Wallace (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Research material about Jean Weisinger (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Research material about Cornell West (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Research material about Andrea E. Woods (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Research material about Malcolm X (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Research material about Lola Young (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Research material about Yearning (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Research material about Molefi Asante (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Research material about Black Ink Comic Exhibit (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Research material about Houston Baker (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Research material about Concerned Black Men (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Research material about race and identity (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Magazine articles (Box 8, Folder 1)
      Research material - race and identity
    - Magazines (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Photocopied articles from magazines and newspapers (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper articles (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper articles (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper articles (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Spiral bound Notepad (Box 56, Folder 8)
      Riggs's hand written production notebook for Black Is...Black Ain't
    - BIBA script notes (Box 56, Folder 9)
      also floppy disc with BIBA outline
    - Photocopied list of information sources and resources for BIBA research (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - BIBA: ITVS 1994 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - BIBA: ITVS 1996 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - BIBA: ITVS 1997-1998 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - BIBA: ITVS 1999 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - BIBA: California Newsreel 1994 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - BIBA: California Newsreel 1995 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - BIBA: Miscellaneous Information (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - BIBA: Supers List (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - BIBA: New York (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - BIBA: Resumes (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - BIBA: Wrap Party 13 Nov 1994 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - BIBA: Letters of Interest (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - BIBA: Storage (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - BIBA: Nicole (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - BIBA: Facilitators Guide (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Mail List (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Telephone message notepad 1994 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Telephone message notepad 1994 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Photocopied newspaper and magazines (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Photocopied newspaper and magazines (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Photocopied newspaper and magazines (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Photocopied newspaper and magazines (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - BIBA - informational promotional postcards (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - BIBA - a Facilitators Guide (Box 58, Folder 11)
      Program notes, Discussion questions and information about the film and its makers (15 copies)
    - Black Is...Black Ain't MTR Taxes (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Black Is...Black Ain't Budget 1992 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Black Is...Black Ain't Budget 1993 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Black Is...Black Ain't Budget 1994 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Black Is...Black Ain't Literary Rights - N.Giovanni (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Black Is...Black Ain't Footage Research (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Black Is...Black Ain't Music Research (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Black Is...Black Ain't Photo Research I (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Black Is...Black Ain't Photo Research II (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Black Is...Black Ain't Travel and production (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Black Is...Black Ain't Logs 1 (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Black Is...Black Ain't Logs 2 (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - Black Is...Black Ain't Production (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - Black Is...Black Ain't Progress Reports (Box 111, Folder 14)
    - Black Is...Black Ain't Transcripts (Box 111, Folder 15)
    - Black Is...Black Ain't Research Quotes (Box 111, Folder 16)
    - Black Is...Black Ain't Production notes and lists (Box 111, Folder 17)
    - Black Is...Black Ain't Script notes (Box 111, Folder 18)
    - Black Is...Black Ain't Oakland shoot (Box 111, Folder 19)
    - Black Is...Black Ain't Marketing proposal (Box 111, Folder 20)
    - 12 items - Various notebooks (Flat-box 112)
      Spiral bound and wireless ruled notebooks with notes about BIBA project
    - BIBA Log List (Flat-box 154)
      Duplicate list of BIBA tape Nos and subject coverage for each tape
    - BIBA Shooting Schedules - Various places (Flat-box 155, Folder 1)
    - BIBA Production notes and reports (Flat-box 155, Folder 2)
    - BIBA Production notes and reports (Flat-box 155, Folder 3)
      Los Angeles
    - BIBA Production notes and reports (Flat-box 155, Folder 4)
      New Orleans
    - BIBA Production notes and reports (Flat-box 155, Folder 5)
      Washington, DC
    - BIBA Production notes and reports (Flat-box 155, Folder 6)
      Mississippi Delta
    - BIBA Production notes and reports (Flat-box 155, Folder 7)
      South Carolina
    - BIBA Handwritten notes for production in LA and NOLA (Flat-box 155, Folder 8)
    - BIBA Handwritten notes for production in DC, Miss, and SC (Flat-box 155, Folder 9)
    - BIBA - Interview transcripts (Box 164)
      from New Orleans, Washington, Virginia, West Indian Day Parade, and Philadelphia, with Time Codes and notes
    - BIBA - Interview transcripts (Box 165)
      from Philadelphia, Southern and Northern California, Missippi and New York, with Time Codes and notes
    - Amistad Resources Center - Research Correspondence (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - BIBA Photos - Archive Photos Research (Box 204, Folder 2)
      Photocopies of research photographs and correspondence
    - BIBA Photos - Beinecke Library Research (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - BIBA Photos - Bettmann Archives Research (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - BIBA Photos - Bob Fletcher (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - BIBA Photos - Impact Visuals (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - BIBA Photos - Ingrid Pollard (Box 204, Folder 7)
    - BIBA Photos - Ken Light (Box 204, Folder 8)
    - BIBA Photos - Library of Congress Research (Box 204, Folder 9)
    - BIBA Photos - Moorland-Springarn (Box 204, Folder 10)
    - BIBA Photos - Robert Haggins (Box 204, Folder 11)
    - BIBA Photos - Lyle Ashton Harris (Box 204, Folder 12)
    - BIBA Photos - T. Johnson (Box 204, Folder 13)
    - BIBA Photos - Sheen Educational Foundation (Box 204, Folder 14)
    - BIBA Photos - R.Sengstacke (Box 204, Folder 15)
    - BIBA Photos - Schomberg (Box 204, Folder 16)
    - BIBA Photos - Schomberg Prints (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - BIBA Photos - Schomberg (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - BIBA Photos - C. Van Vechten (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - BIBA Photos - J. Weisinger (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - BIBA Photos - Wide World Photos (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - BIBA Photos - White on Black (Box 205, Folder 6)
    - BIBA Photos - Xavier University archives (Box 205, Folder 7)
    - BIBA Research - Jackys Research (Box 205, Folder 8)
    - BIBA Research - Quotes (Box 205, Folder 9)
    - BIBA Research - Papers (Box 205, Folder 10)
    - BIBA Research - Photocopied material (Box 205, Folder 11)
    - BIBA Research - Print outs (Box 205, Folder 12)
    - BIBA Research - Misc notes (Box 205, Folder 13)
    - BIBA Research - University of Florida (Box 205, Folder 14)
    - BIBA Research - Expenditure (Box 205, Folder 15)
    - BIBA Application, 1991 (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - BIBA Contracts - Personnel (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - BIBA Contracts - ITVS (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - BIBA ITVS - Reports (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - BIBA ITVS - Correspondence 1 (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - BIBA ITVS - Correspondence 2 (Box 206, Folder 6)
    - BIBA California Newsreel - Correspondence (Box 206, Folder 7)
    - BIBA California Newsreel - income (Box 206, Folder 8)
    - BIBA Closed Caption/VTE (Box 206, Folder 9)
    - BIBA Correspondence - general (Box 206, Folder 10)
    - BIBA Donations (Box 206, Folder 11)
    - BIBA Dubs sent out (Box 206, Folder 12)
    - BIBA Edit List (Box 206, Folder 13)
    - BIBA Film Findings (Box 206, Folder 14)
    - BIBA French Distribution (Box 206, Folder 15)
    - BIBA Footage Cue Sheet (Box 206, Folder 16)
    - BIBA Films Transit (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - BIBA Films Transit Inc (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - BIBA Festivals - Entry forms submitted, 1995 (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - BIBA Festivals - Awards (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - BIBA Festivals - Ann Arbor Film Festival (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - BIBA Festivals - Atlanta Film & Video Festival (Box 207, Folder 6)
    - BIBA Festivals - Berlin, 1995 (Box 207, Folder 7)
    - BIBA Festivals - Birmingham, UK (Box 207, Folder 8)
    - BIBA Festivals - Black Filmmakers Hall of Fame (Box 207, Folder 9)
    - BIBA Festivals - Carolina Film & Video Festival (Box 207, Folder 10)
    - BIBA Festivals - Charlotte Film & Video Festival (Box 207, Folder 11)
    - BIBA Festivals - Cinema du Reel (Box 207, Folder 12)
    - BIBA Festivals - Dallas, 1994 (Box 207, Folder 13)
    - BIBA Festivals - FESPACO, Burkino Faso, 1995 (Box 207, Folder 14)
    - BIBA Festivals - Film Arts Foundation (Box 207, Folder 15)
    - BIBA Festivals - Florida Film Festival (Box 207, Folder 16)
    - BIBA Festivals - Black Maria, 1994 (Box 207, Folder 17)
    - BIBA Festivals - Input (Box 207, Folder 18)
    - BIBA Festivals - London Film Festival (Box 207, Folder 19)
    - BIBA Festivals - London Gay & Lesbian Film Festival (Box 207, Folder 20)
    - BIBA Festivals - Los Angeles Gay & Lesbian Film Festival (Box 207, Folder 21)
    - BIBA Festivals - New York Lesbian & Gay Film Festival (Box 207, Folder 22)
    - BIBA Festivals - Newark Black Film Festival (Box 207, Folder 23)
    - BIBA Festivals - National Educational Media Festival, 1995 (Box 207, Folder 24)
    - BIBA Festivals - Out of Africa Film festival (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - BIBA Festivals - Paris Gay & Lesbian Film Festival (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - BIBA Festivals - Pride Film Festival (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - BIBA Festivals - Santa Barbara Lesbian & Gay Film Festival (Box 208, Folder 4)
    - BIBA Festivals - San Francisco International Film Festival, 1995 (Box 208, Folder 5)
    - BIBA Festivals - Seattle International Film festival, 1995 (Box 208, Folder 6)
    - BIBA Festivals - Sinking Creek (Box 208, Folder 7)
    - BIBA Festivals - Sundance, 1995 (Box 208, Folder 8)
    - BIBA Festivals - Sydney Film Festival, 1995 (Box 208, Folder 9)
    - BIBA Festivals - Tel Aviv Cinematheque (Box 208, Folder 10)
    - BIBA Festivals - Wellington - Auckland Film Festival (Box 208, Folder 11)
    - BIBA Festivals - Programs (Box 208, Folder 12)
    - BIBA Festivals - Submitted by Tara/CA Newsreel (Box 208, Folder 13)
    - BIBA Festivals - Possible festivals for submission (Box 208, Folder 14)
    - BIBA Festivals - International Festival Hopefuls (Box 208, Folder 15)
    - BIBA Tara Releasing (Box 208, Folder 16)
    - BIBA Film Transfer Information (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - BIBA Funding Exchange Contract (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - BIBA Funding - Robeson Fund (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - BIBA Funding - California Council for the Humanities (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - BIBA Funding - LEF Foundation (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - BIBA Funding - National Black Programming Consortium (Box 209, Folder 6)
    - BIBA Funding - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 209, Folder 7)
    - BIBA Funding - NEA Correspondence (Box 209, Folder 8)
    - BIBA Funding - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 209, Folder 9)
    - BIBA Funding - Western States Regional Media Arts Fellowship (Box 209, Folder 10)
    - BIBA Funding - Zellerbach Family Fund (Box 209, Folder 11)
    - BIBA Funding - Ford Foundation (Box 209, Folder 12)
    - BIBA Funding - Gerbode Foundation (Box 209, Folder 13)
    - BIBA Funding - Kaiser Foundation (Box 209, Folder 14)
    - BIBA ITVS Grant income (Box 209, Folder 15)
    - BIBA Cast and Crew Contact List (Box 209, Folder 16)
    - BIBA Final production Budget, 1994 (Box 209, Folder 17)
    - BIBA Final script (Box 209, Folder 18)
    - BIBA Final credit Lists (Box 209, Folder 19)
    - BIBA Progress Report (Box 209, Folder 20)
    - BIBA Private contributions list (Box 209, Folder 21)
    - BIBA International Documentary awards (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - BIBA Presale Inquiries Channel 4 (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - BIBA Presale Inquiries BBC (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - BIBA Isaac Julien (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - BIBA Legal - Barbara Koppel (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - BIBA Press Information (Box 210, Folder 6)
    - BIBA Conference Bookings (Box 210, Folder 7)
    - BIBA Certificates from various festivals (Box 210, Folder 8)
    - BIBA Releases - Academics (Box 210, Folder 9)
    - BIBA Releases - London (Box 210, Folder 10)
    - BIBA Releases - Mississippi (Box 210, Folder 11)
    - BIBA Releases - Los Angeles (Box 210, Folder 12)
    - BIBA Releases - New York (Box 210, Folder 13)
    - BIBA Releases - New Orleans (Box 210, Folder 14)
    - BIBA Releases - Oakland (Box 210, Folder 15)
    - BIBA Releases - Shelton 1 (Box 210, Folder 16)
    - BIBA Releases - Shelton 2 (Box 210, Folder 17)
    - BIBA Releases - South Carolina (Box 210, Folder 18)
    - BIBA Releases - Step Show (Box 210, Folder 19)
    - BIBA Releases - Washington DC (Box 210, Folder 20)
    - BIBA Screenings UK (Box 210, Folder 21)
    - BIBA Screenings BFI (Box 210, Folder 22)
    - BIBA Screenings 1995 (Box 210, Folder 23)
    - BIBA Reviews (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - BIBA Reviews (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - BIBA Reviews (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - BIBA Reviews (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - BIBA Cue Sheets - Archival Footage (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - BIBA Cue Sheets - Music (Box 211, Folder 6)
    - BIBA Cue Sheets - Photos (Box 211, Folder 7)
    - BIBA Footage - Archive Films (Box 211, Folder 8)
    - BIBA Footage - CBS News Archives (Box 211, Folder 9)
    - BIBA Footage - Fallen Champ (Box 211, Folder 10)
    - BIBA Footage - Grinberg (Box 211, Folder 11)
    - BIBA Footage - KPIX (Box 211, Folder 12)
    - BIBA Footage - KQED (Box 211, Folder 13)
    - BIBA Footage - KRON (Box 211, Folder 14)
    - BIBA Footage - KTVU (Box 211, Folder 15)
    - BIBA Footage - Mississippi (Box 211, Folder 16)
    - BIBA Footage - NBC News Archives (Box 211, Folder 17)
    - BIBA Footage - Olympics (Box 211, Folder 18)
    - BIBA Footage - Petrified (Box 211, Folder 19)
    - BIBA Footage - Library of Congress (Box 211, Folder 20)
    - BIBA Footage - Donahue (Box 211, Folder 21)
    - BIBA Footage - Signifyin Works (Box 211, Folder 22)
    - BIBA Footage - Portrait of Jason (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - BIBA Footage - Herdsmen of the Sun (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - BIBA Footage - Raw (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - BIBA Footage - Fox Movietone (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - BIBA Literary Quotes (Box 212, Folder 5)
    - BIBA Music Notes (Box 212, Folder 6)
    - BIBA Music - Blues Band (Box 212, Folder 7)
    - BIBA Music - Drummers (Box 212, Folder 8)
    - BIBA Music - Harry Fox Agency (Box 212, Folder 9)
    - BIBA Music - Mary Watkins (Box 212, Folder 10)
    - BIBA Music - 'Been in the storm so long' (Box 212, Folder 11)
    - BIBA Music - 'Dust my Broom' (Box 212, Folder 12)
    - BIBA Music - 'Focus on Sanity' (Box 212, Folder 13)
    - BIBA Music - 'Ghetto Theme' (Box 212, Folder 14)
    - BIBA Music - 'Handa Wanda' (Box 212, Folder 15)
    - BIBA Music - 'Hold that Tiger' (Box 212, Folder 16)
    - BIBA Music - 'How Long?' (Box 212, Folder 17)
    - BIBA Music - 'Let us break bread' (Box 212, Folder 18)
    - BIBA Music - 'Lift every voice' (Box 212, Folder 19)
    - BIBA Music - 'Little coquette' (Box 212, Folder 20)
    - BIBA Music - 'Living in a Jungle' (Box 212, Folder 21)
    - BIBA Music - 'In Memoriam Uncle Dan' (Box 212, Folder 22)
    - BIBA Music - 'Niama' (Box 212, Folder 23)
    - BIBA Music - 'Power of Love' (Box 212, Folder 24)
    - BIBA Music - 'Remember Me' (Box 212, Folder 25)
    - BIBA Music - 'Say it Loud' (Box 212, Folder 26)
    - BIBA Music - 'Socio-Genetic Experiment' (Box 212, Folder 27)
    - BIBA Music - 'So Swell when you're Well' (Box 212, Folder 28)
    - BIBA Music - 'Southern Women Blues' (Box 212, Folder 29)
    - BIBA Music - 'To Be Young, Gifted and Black' (Box 212, Folder 30)
    - BIBA Music - 'True to the Game' (Half-box 213, Folder 1)
    - BIBA Music - 'Unity' (Half-box 213, Folder 2)
    - BIBA Music - 'Uptown Anthem' (Half-box 213, Folder 3)
    - BIBA Music - 'Washed Away' (Half-box 213, Folder 4)
    - BIBA Music - 'We shall not be moved' (Half-box 213, Folder 5)
    - BIBA Music - 'We shall overcome' (Half-box 213, Folder 6)
    - BIBA Music - 'Woman' (Half-box 213, Folder 7)
    - BIBA Music - 'You Gotta Move' (Half-box 213, Folder 8)
    - BIBA Logs (Box 220, Folder 1)
    - BIBA Script 1993 (Box 220, Folder 2)
    - BIBA Script 1994 (Box 220, Folder 3)
    - BIBA Final Scripts with notes (Box 220, Folder 4)
    - BIBA Selects (Box 220, Folder 5)
    - BIBA Production (Box 220, Folder 6)
    - BIBA Production Schedules (Box 220, Folder 7)
    - BIBA Black Parades (Box 221, Folder 1)
    - BIBA Cash Flow projections (Box 221, Folder 2)
    - BIBA Carnet Application (London) (Box 221, Folder 3)
    - BIBA Employee Information (Box 221, Folder 4)
    - BIBA Equipment Rentals (Box 221, Folder 5)
    - BIBA Interview Questions (Box 221, Folder 6)
    - BIBA Legal information (Box 221, Folder 7)
    - BIBA London Filming Shoot (Box 221, Folder 8)
    - BIBALos Angeles Filming Shoot 1992 (Box 221, Folder 9)
    - BIBA Mississippi (Box 221, Folder 10)
    - BIBA New Orleans (Box 221, Folder 11)
    - BIBA Notes from Carroll Blue (Box 221, Folder 12)
    - BIBA Oyotunji Village (Box 221, Folder 13)
    - BIBA Poetry (Box 221, Folder 14)
    - BIBA Press Kit Info (Half-box 222, Folder 1)
    - BIBA Release forms (Half-box 222, Folder 2)
    - BIBA Resource List (Half-box 222, Folder 3)
    - BIBA Correspondences (Half-box 222, Folder 4)
    - BIBA Sea Island (Half-box 222, Folder 5)
    - BIBA Sheltons Primary Education Center (Half-box 222, Folder 6)
    - BIBA Texas (Half-box 222, Folder 7)
    - BIBA West Coast Stepping show (Half-box 222, Folder 8)
    - BIBA Travel Information (Half-box 222, Folder 9)
    - Black Filmmakers Hall of Fame (Flat-box 226, Folder 29)
      Best Film Overall award to Riggs for Black Is...Black Ain't, 1995
    - Black Filmmakers Hall of Fame (Flat-box 226, Folder 30)
      First Place Documentary section award to Riggs for Black Is...Black Ain't, 1995
  - Subseries 9: Other Projects
    - Espresso Productions information (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Espresso Productions paychecks 1982 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Project Papers: How Much is Enough?, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Project Papers: How Much is Enough?, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Project Papers: The First Fifty Years: Reflections on US/Soviet Relations, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Project Papers: In other Words: The State of Language (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Project Papers:In Our Defence (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Project Papers: Warring Ideals, Henry O. Tanner film project, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Project Papers: A Travelling Jewish Theatre, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Project Papers: Faces of War, Central America, PBS, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Project Papers: Changing Images: Mirrors of Life Molds of Reality, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      also audio cassette of narration
    - Project Papers: Facing History, Brooklyn Museum Project, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Project Proposal: VTT, Visions Toward Tomorrow, 1988/9 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Project Papers: VTT Berkeley Research (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Project Papers: VTT Research (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Project Papers: VTT Oakland Research (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Project Papers: VTT Richmond Research (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - California Newsreel brochure of Video Library items (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - California Newsreel (Box 58, Folder 7)
      African American Perspectives 1996-1997 - brochure of films available (2 copies)
    - Mongrel Media Brochures of Videos available (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Brochure of 5th Festival of 'Visions of Elsewhere' entitled 'The Other Image of America' (Box 58, Folder 9)
      Shown at the Expressions Film Center in Udine, Italy in Oct/Nov 2000
    - Correspondence - Misc - Persea Books letter, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Project Papers: Reconstruction Bibliography (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Project Papers: Reconstruction Consultants Meeting (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Project Papers: Reconstruction - general papers (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Project Papers: Reconstruction Research (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Project Papers: Reconstruction Articles (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Project Papers: Called Forth (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Project Papers: Changing Images (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Project Papers: Visions toward Tomorrow (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Project Papers: Black America (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Project Papers: The Conjurers (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Censorship - photocopied article (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Project Papers: Recovery (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Project Papers: Rap (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Project Papers: Porn (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Project Papers: Tanner (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Project Papers: Miscellaneous projects (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Project Papers: Muses (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Project Papers: Testing the Limits (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Project Papers: Trails (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - BIBA Correspondence (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Various notebooks from projects (Flat-box 95)
    - Various Film Festival Programs and Brochures (Flat-box 172)
    - Faces of War (Half-box 177, Folder 5)
    - Faces of War - EDL (Half-box 177, Folder 6)
    - Faces of War - Narration (Half-box 177, Folder 7)
    - Faces of War - EDL (Half-box 177, Folder 8)
    - Book Cover - 'Other Countries' Black Gay Voices (Flat-box 215, Folder 6)
    - Video Audio File (Flat-box 215, Folder 7)
    - Visions toward tomorrow - teachers guide (Flat-box 215, Folder 10)
    - Film Festival Programs, 1995 (Flat-box 215, Folder 13)